Guide to the Helen and Newton Harrison Papers M1797
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 17. Audiovisual Material, 1971-2011
  - Horton Plaza Environmental Impact Study; Side 1: Levy + Us, Side 2: Question 1+2, 1977; M1797_bav14_009 (Box AV 14, Audiocassette M1797_bav14_009)
  - Horton Plaza Environmental Impact Study; Side 1: Levy + Us, Horton Plaza, 1977; M1797_bav14_010 (Box AV 14, Audiocassette M1797_bav14_010)
  - Harrison Interview, 1977; M1797_bav14_011 (Box AV 14, Audiocassette M1797_bav14_011)
  - Harrison's Tape, Talk at San Jose State University, 1983; M1797_bav14_012 (Box AV 14, Audiocassette M1797_bav14_012)
  - Harrison's Tape, Talk at San Jose State University, 1983; M1797_bav14_013 (Box AV 14, Audiocassette M1797_bav14_013)
  - Newton on work, undated; M1797_bav14_014 (Box AV 14, Audiocassette M1797_bav14_014)
    Side 1: Comparison of two novels "A Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man" and "The Ginger Man" by unknown person Side 2: Newton on work
  - KCRW- Art Talk: Edward Goldman on Maurice Tuchman and LACMA, April 12, 1993; M1797_bav14_015 (Box AV 14, Audiocassette M1797_bav14_015)
  - KBOO, Radiozine -Art Focus: Julie Bernard, The Harrisons, January 28, 1993; M1797_bav14_016 (Box AV 14, Audiocassette M1797_bav14_016)
  - KBOO, Radiozine -Art Focus: Julie Bernard, Newton Harrison, KBOO 90.7 FM, December 10, 1992; M1797_bav14_017 (Box AV 14, Audiocassette M1797_bav14_017)
  - Baltimore Promenade, Performance, Washington Project for the Arts, December 3, 1992; M1797_bav14_018 (Box AV 14, Audiocassette M1797_bav14_018)
  - I. Symposium: Art and Ecology – Visions, Collaborations, Enactments, August 3, 2001; M1797_bav15_001 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_001)
  - II. Symposium: Art and Ecology – Visions, Collaborations, Enactments, August 3, 2001; M1797_bav15_002 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_002)
  - III. Potsdam Conference: Art and Ecology – Visions, Collaborations, Enactments, August 3, 2001; M1797_bav15_003 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_003)
  - IV. Symposium: Art and Ecology – Visions, Collaborations, Enactments, August 3, 2001; M1797_bav15_004 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_004)
  - V. Symposium: Art and Ecology – Visions, Collaborations, Enactments, August 4, 2001; M1797_bav15_005 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_005)
  - VI. Symposium: Art and Ecology – Visions, Collaborations, Enactments, August 4, 2001; M1797_bav15_006 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_006)
  - VII. Symposium: Art and Ecology – Visions, Collaborations, Enactments, August 4, 2001; M1797_bav15_007 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_007)
  - Committee of the Whole, A) Guadalupe River / Coyote Creek B. Coyote Creek & impact on Quadflow, plus Alviso resident response, February 1, 1983; M1797_bav15_008 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_008)
    Recording of local meeting regarding river flooding in San Jose.
  - David Antin on Color, undated; M1797_bav15_009 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_009)
    An academic lecture and discussion on color and sculpture.
  - David Antin on Nancy Graves, undated; M1797_bav15_010 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_010)
    An academic lecture and discussion on semiotics and Nancy Graves.
  - Daniel Buren, undated; M1797_bav15_011 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_011)
  - Desautels #1, undated; M1797_bav15_012 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_012)
    Informational interview with archaeologist Roger J. Desautels on Chu'umsh people and Orange County by unnamed person.
  - Desautels #2, undated; M1797_bav15_013 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_013)
  - Max Neuhaus interview, All Things Considered, National Public Radio, 1980; M1797_bav15_014 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_014)
  - The San Andreas Fault of California, 1974; M1797_bav15_015 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_015)
  - 2 Mandolins by Len + Dan Bergantino, 1991; M1797_bav15_016 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_016)
  - Len Bergantino, undated; M1797_bav15_017 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_017)
  - Joy Eden Harrison, 1998; M1797_bav15_018 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_018)
    Side A. 40 Days 40 Nights, Pushing My Luck, Graveyards, Everybody's Good Time Girl, Rubberband, The Secret Side; B. Leap In The Dark, Reluctant Angel, Words, Yellow, The Innocence Begins Again
  - Joy Eden Harrison in Concert, 1988; M1797_bav15_019 (Box AV 15, Audiocassette M1797_bav15_019)
    A. In Concert, Warburg Germany; B. At home in Solana Beach; A Publishing Demo
  - Armageddon: The Rose, The Blade And The Fools Crusade, New Era, 1985; M1797_bav16_001 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_001)
  - Elliott: Why I Dyed My Hair Red (And Other White Lies), 1989; M1797_bav16_002 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_002)
  - D.A.Z. Document (des alltags zorn document), töne aum dem abraum, 1992; M1797_bav16_003 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_003)
  - Angels Have Been Sent to Me, an interactive art experience / Me Han Mando Angeles, una experiencia de arte interactiva, 1991; M1797_bav16_004 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_004)
  - IDCA 1993, Reconstruction Ahead, #4 - Is Ecology Useful?, M1797_bav16_005 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_005)
  - Excerpts from Lil Willie: Peas & Rice Press (in progress), 1990; M1797_bav16_006 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_006)
    by Johnny Coleman
  - Excerpts from Lil Willie: Peas & Rice Press (in progress), 1990; M1797_bav16_007 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_007)
  - Diane Hamilton, Demo, undated; M1797_bav16_008 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_008)
  - Upali Senanayake - The Meaning of the Flag, 1972; M1797_bav16_009 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_009)
  - Recording of Pasadena For The Year 2000 Committee meeting, 1987; M1797_bav16_010 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_010)
    Mislabeled as "Isle of Skye, Cindy Kallet"
  - John Stevens, 1987; M1797_bav16_011 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_011)
    1. Transit Shifts for Solo Violin, János Négyesy - Violin; 2. Penas, La Jolla Wind Quintet; 3. The Evolution of Madness, Computer Tape
  - Joy Eden Harrison, undated; M1797_bav16_012 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_012)
  - Conversation and stroke therapy with Helen, Mrs. Weisman, and unnamed person, undated; M1797_bav16_013 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_013)
  - Untitled readings of Helen and Newton on their collaboration, undated; M1797_bav16_014 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_014)
  - Untitled description of a Jud Fine exhibition at La Jolla Museum of Contemporary Art, 1988; M1797_bav16_015 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_015)
  - Untitled outgoing voicemail message, undated; M1797_bav16_016 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_016)
  - Untitled discussion with Helen, Newton, and unnamed person, undated; M1797_bav16_017 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_017)
  - Untitled reading and discussion of "Bargain" from The Big It and Other Stories by A. B. Guthrie, undated; M1797_bav16_018 (Box AV 16, Audiocassette M1797_bav16_018)
  - Untitled performance of Great Lakes Meditations, 1977; M1797_bav17_001 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_001)
  - Untitled conversation and stroke therapy with Helen, Mrs. Weisman, and unnamed person, undated; M1797_bav17_002 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_002)
  - Untitled reading from notes of interview with Helen and Newton, 1992; M1797_bav17_003 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_003)
  - Untitled audiocassette, 1988; M1797_bav17_004 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_004)
  - Excerpts From "The Lagoon Cycle", the introductory panel, 1984; M1797_bav17_005 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_005)
  - Untitled performance of "Me and Bobby McGee", "500 miles" and other songs, undated; M1797_bav17_006 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_006)
  - Helen singing "White Christmas", undated; M1797_bav17_007 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_007)
  - Untitled musical recording of the band Dead Can Dance, undated; M1797_bav17_008 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_008)
    Commercially available, not reformatted.
  - Profiles in Violence, Family Practice, Vol 42, No. 32, 1994; M1797_bav17_009 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_009)
    Commercially produced, not reformatted.
  - Progressive Relaxation Training, 1980; M1797_bav17_010 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_010)
  - General Relaxation, Biofeedback Institute of San Diego, undated; M1797_bav17_011 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_011)
  - Serbo-Croatian for Travelers, 1974; M1797_bav17_012 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_012)
  - Latin-American Spanish Phrase cassette, 1992; M1797_bav17_013 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_013)
  - Living Language, German, 1993; M1797_bav17_014 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_014)
  - Barron's Japanese At A Glance, 1985; M1797_bav17_015 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_015)
  - Just Listen 'n Learn, German, 1982; M1797_bav17_016 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_016)
  - Gould plays Bach; Italian Concerto, Preludes, Fuges, Dances, 1983; M1797_bav17_017 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_017)
  - Deutsche Grammophon, Johann Sebastian Bach, 1971; M1797_bav17_018 (Box AV 17, Audiocassette M1797_bav17_018)
  - Deutsche Grammophon, Bach, 1968; M1797_bav18_001 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_001)
  - Deutsche Grammophon, Antonio Vivald, 1969; M1797_bav18_002 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_002)
  - Beethoven, Symphony No. 9 In D Minor, 'Coral', Dresden Philharmonic, 1984; M1797_bav18_003 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_003)
  - Felix Mendelssohn, 1983; M1797_bav18_004 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_004)
  - Walkman Classics, Beethoven: Symphonies 5 & 6, 1972; M1797_bav18_005 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_005)
  - Chopin's Greatest Hits, 1984; M1797_bav18_006 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_006)
  - Vladimir Horowitz, My Favorite Chopin, 1984; M1797_bav18_007 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_007)
  - Royce Rolls, poetry and reading by Royce Dendler, undated; M1797_bav18_008 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_008)
  - The Other Side of Round Midnight, 1986; M1797_bav18_009 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_009)
  - These Were Our Early Songs, The Early '30s, 1989; M1797_bav18_010 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_010)
  - Remember The Love, 1991; M1797_bav18_011 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_011)
  - Guarneri Quartet - Haydn: String Quartets, 1980; M1797_bav18_012 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_012)
  - Fröhliche Weihnachten!, Bläser Quintett St. Petersburg, Russland, 1997; M1797_bav18_013 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_013)
  - Sounds of the Holiday Season, 1992; M1797_bav18_014 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_014)
  - Kiss Me Kate, Original MGM Soundtrack, 1990; M1797_bav18_015 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_015)
  - My Fair Lady, Original 1956 Broadway Cast Recording, undated; M1797_bav18_016 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_016)
  - Cole Porter Songbook, 1996; M1797_bav18_017 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_017)
  - Walkman Classics, Mozart: Eine kleine Nachtmusik, Serenata nottirna, Divertimenti, Sinfonia Concertante, 1976; M1797_bav18_018 (Box AV 18, Audiocassette M1797_bav18_018)
  - Deutsche Grammophon, Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart, 1984; M1797_bav19_001 (Box AV 19, Audiocassette M1797_bav19_001)
  - The Best of Broadway Musicals, Vol 1, undated; M1797_bav19_002 (Box AV 19, Audiocassette M1797_bav19_002)
  - The Best of Broadway Musicals, Vol 2, undated; M1797_bav19_003 (Box AV 19, Audiocassette M1797_bav19_003)
  - Newton and Helen, Peninsula Europe, 2001; M1797_bav20_001 (Box AV 20, Videotape M1797_bav20_001)
    Audio is noise only; video is high quality.
  - Altering Discourse: The Works of Helen and Newton Harrison; Colorado State, Master, 2000; M1797_bav20_002 (Box AV 20, Videotape M1797_bav20_002)
  - Annie Sprinkle's Amazing World of Orgasm, 2004; M1797_bav20_003 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_003)
    Adult content.
  - Regret to Inform, 1998; M1797_bav20_004 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_004)
  - The Serpentine Lattice, 1995; M1797_bav20_005 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_005)
  - Ecological Networks, Dream or Reality?, 2002; M1797_bav20_006 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_006)
  - Unnatural Disaster, 1991; M1797_bav20_007 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_007)
    Appears to be a program from part of a promotional reel for producer-director Simon Bowler.
  - Arturo Toscanini, NBC Symphony Orchestra, Ludwig van Beethoven, Vol. 1, 1998; M1797_bav20_008 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_008)
  - Tomorrow's Climate, Today's Challenge, 2005; M1797_bav20_010 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_010)
  - EM (Effective Microorganisms) and Water, 1994; M1797_bav20_011 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_011)
  - Crisis as Opportunity: Living Better on a Hotter Planet; Elisabet Sahtouris, 2007; M1797_bav20_012 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_012)
  - Holland & others, 1994; M1797_bav20_013 (Box AV 20, Compact disc M1797_bav20_013)
  - Saving the Bay, The Story of San Francisco Bay, 2009; M1797_bav20_014 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_014)
    Promotional video for 4 part PBS documentary Saving the Bay, The Story of San Francisco Bay.
  - Knowle West Media Centre, Paradise Found, 2007; M1797_bav20_015 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_015)
  - Knowle West Media Centre, Defeat the Heat, 2006; M1797_bav20_016 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_016)
  - Knowle West Media Centre, West Goes East, 2007; M1797_bav20_017 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_017)
  - Knowle West Media Centre, Think or Swim, 2007; M1797_bav20_018 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_018)
  - Knowle West Media Centre, Think or Swim, 2007; M1797_bav20_019 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_019)
  - The Serpentine Lattice, 1995; M1797_bav20_020 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_020)
    Harrison team supplies voice over narrative to "The Serpentine Lattice" panels.
  - Greenhouse Britain, Losing Ground, Gaining Wisdom, First Edit, 2008; M1797_bav20_026 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_026)
  - Santa Fe Watershed: Lessons from the Genius of Place, 2005; M1797_bav20_027 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_027)
  - Future Garden, Kunst-und Ausstellungshalle, Bonn, 1997; M1797_bav20_028 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_028)
  - Future Garden, Kunst-und Ausstellungshalle, Bonn, 1997; M1797_bav20_029 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_029)
  - Serpentine Lattice, 1995; M1797_bav20_031 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_031)
  - The Jefferson Exchange, Jefferson Public Radio, October 31, 2005; M1797_bav20_032 (Box AV 20, Compact disc M1797_bav20_032)
  - Newton & Helen Harrison, June 14, 2006; M1797_bav20_033 (Box AV 20, Compact disc M1797_bav20_033)
  - Talking Water, Feldman Gallery, 1980's; Altering Discourse: The Works of Helen and Newton Harrison; Colorado State Lecture, 2000; M1797_bav20_034 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_034)
  - Curitiba: More For Less, undated; M1797_bav20_035 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_035)
  - Rivers Institute at the University of Dayton, 2000; M1797_bav20_037 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_037)
    Professionally produced PSA from the Rivers Institute
  - The Mountain in the Greenhouse, 2001; M1797_bav20_039 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_039)
    Professionally produced animation
  - The Mountain in the Greenhouse, 2001; M1797_bav20_040 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_040)
  - Sierra Nevada: An Adaptation Opening Feldman Fine Arts, 2011; M1797_bav20_041 (Box AV 20, Compact disc M1797_bav20_041)
  - "KW Forest" DVD, February 4, 2008; M1797_bav20_042 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_042)
  - Independence- Lake, animations, 2011; M1797_bav20_043 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_043)
  - Independence Lake, animation, Video 2, 2011; M1797_bav20_044 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_044)
  - Independence Lake, animation, Video 1, 2011; M1797_bav20_045 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_045)
  - Santa Fe Watershed: Lessons from the Genius of Place, 2005; M1797_bav20_046 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_046)
  - Radical Nature-Barbican, 2009; M1797_bav20_047 (Box AV 20, Compact disc M1797_bav20_047)
  - The View from the Center of the Universe, October 25, 2006; M1797_bav20_048 (Box AV 20, Videodisc M1797_bav20_048)
  - The Serpentine Lattice, Edited Master, February 22, 1993; M1797_bav21_002 (Box AV 21, Reel M1797_bav21_002)
  - New Arts, 1971; M1797_bav21_003 (Box AV 21, Reel M1797_bav21_003)
    Documentation of the Art & Technology works exhibited at Expo ’70.
  - Documentation Survival Series No. 2-6, on portable farming, harvesting, and feasting by Newton Harrison, 1972; M1797_bav21_004 (Box AV 21, Reel M1797_bav21_004)
  - Documentation Survival Series No. 2-6, on portable farming, harvesting, and feasting by Newton Harrison, 1972; M1797_bav21_005 (Box AV 21, Reel M1797_bav21_005)
  - NH's Survival Series, No. 2-5 (6), 1972; M1797_bav21_006 (Box AV 21, Reel M1797_bav21_006)
    Audio only
  - Survival Series by NH, 1972; M1797_bav21_007 (Box AV 21, Reel M1797_bav21_007)
  - Untitled landscape, Italy, 1974; M1797_bav21_008 (Box AV 21, Reel M1797_bav21_008)
    Most likely Bicocchi family farm.
  - Untitled landscape, Italy, 1974; M1797_bav21_009 (Box AV 21, Reel M1797_bav21_009)
  - Untitled landscape, Italy, 1974; M1797_bav21_010 (Box AV 21, Reel M1797_bav21_010)
  - Untitled landscape, Italy, 1974; M1797_bav21_011 (Box AV 21, Reel M1797_bav21_011)
  - Untitled landscape, Italy, 1974; M1797_bav21_012 (Box AV 21, Reel M1797_bav21_012)
  - Untitled landscape, Italy, 1974; M1797_bav21_013 (Box AV 21, Reel M1797_bav21_013)
  - Untitled landscape, Italy, 1974; M1797_bav21_014 (Box AV 21, Reel M1797_bav21_014)
  - ReSources, Saving Living Systems, 2009; M1797_bav22_001 (Box AV 22, Videodisc M1797_bav22_001)
  - Intervene! Interrupt! Keynote Address, May 15, 2008; M1797_bav22_002 (Box AV 22, Videodisc M1797_bav22_002)
  - Independence Lake, animation, Video 1, Widescreen 16x9, 2011; M1797_bav22_003 (Box AV 22, Videodisc M1797_bav22_003)
    Professionally produced animation.
  - Independence Lake, animation, Video 2, Widescreen 16x9, 2011; M1797_bav22_004 (Box AV 22, Videodisc M1797_bav22_004)
  - Independence Lake, animation, Video 1, 4x3, 2011; M1797_bav22_005 (Box AV 22, Videodisc M1797_bav22_005)
  - Independence Lake, animation, Video 2, 4x3, 2011; M1797_bav22_006 (Box AV 22, Videodisc M1797_bav22_006)
  - Atopia animation, Harrison, 2009; M1797_bav22_007 (Box AV 22, Videodisc M1797_bav22_007)
  - From the 7th Lagoon, Ring of Fire, Ring of Water, "One day I heard the ocean singing", 1982; M1797_bav22_008 (Box AV 22, Videodisc M1797_bav22_008)
  - Map Test, 2011; M1797_bav22_009 (Box AV 22, Videodisc M1797_bav22_009)
  - Santa Fe Watershed: Lessons from the Genius of Place, 2005; M1797_bav22_010 (Box AV 22, Videodisc M1797_bav22_010)
- Series 18. Computer Media/Born-Digital, 1990-2016
  This series has been divided into two sub-series: Subseries 1. Email and Subseries 2. Digital Files.
  Unrestricted materials are available on the Media Cart in the Special Collections Reading Room.
  - Subseries 1. Email, 2004-2016
    Email in accessions 2016-053 and 2016-054 were captured from the Harrison Studio Gmail and AOL email accounts with ePADD software resulting in over 77,000 messages. This sub-series is comprised of: 68,110 incoming messages and 9,636 outgoing; 25,145 attachments (7,161 images, 5,466 documents, and 12,518 other); 15,170 correspondents; extracted entities (114,865 persons, 124,823 organizations, and 69,780 locations).
    Materials are available on the Media Cart in the Special Collections Reading Room.
  - Subseries 2. Digital Files, circa 1990-2013
    The material contained in this subseries consists of documents, graphics, spreadsheets, databases, software programs, video, audio, and other material created and/or stored on computers, removable media, and hard drives managed by the Harrisons and their assistants. The digital files are forensically captured images of those stored on hard drives, floppy diskettes, CD-ROMs, zip disks, and other media in the Harrison papers.
    Arrangement
    Tags, corresponding with the existing series arrangement of the physical collection, were added to the digital material. The digital content was arranged and exported by series. Many files are tagged multiple times resulting in the same file appearing in different series. Tagged series are as follows: Series 1. Personal papers; Series 2. Project Files; Series 4. Correspondence; Series 5. Performances and Exhibitions; Series 6. Presentations and Speeches; Series 8. Research; Series 9. Business Records; Series 10. UCSD; Series 11. UCSC; Series 12. Writings; Series 13. Individuals; Series 14. Public Relations Material; Series 15. Photographic Material; Series 17. Audiovisual; Series 19. Artwork and Artifacts
    Computer discs are housed in boxes 263-267.
- Series 19. Art and Artifacts, 1961-1990
  This series contains artwork and artifacts in possession of the Harrisons. Notable items include a piece by Newton Harrison called "The Path" and Fluxus artwork. Material is arranged alphabetically.
  - Fluxus flyers, 1966-1968, undated (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Fluxus kit, 1961-1968, undated (Flat-boxes 303-306)
    Designed and produced by George Maciunas. Artists include George Brecht, Ken Friedman, Takehisha Kosugi, Shigeko Kubota, Serge Oldenbourg, Benjamin Patterson, James Riddle, Mieko Shiomi, Ben Vautier, and Robert Watts.
  - "Forum Spektral" by Hajo Franzky, undated (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - Making Earth Again, 1990 (Flat-box 307)
  - "Mortality (Dedicated to Helen and Newton)", undated (Box 258, Folder 3)
    by unidentified
  - The Path, circa 1969 (Box 308)
    See also: Box 135, Folder 12 Box 163, Folder 19 Map Folder 381
  - Untitled by Mariana and Mark, undated (Box 258, Folder 4)